foreclosuredatabank.com 2018-06-25

# Privacy and Policies Provided by ForeclosureDataBank.com

## Privacy and Information Security Policy

Foreclosuredatabank.com is committed to actively respecting and protecting your personal information in all of our online and offline procedures and processes. This document will explain our Privacy and Information Security Policy, as well as some of the steps we take to maintain your privacy and security when you use our website.

### What personal information you collect

At Foreclosuredatabank.com, we collect information about you when you use our site and provide it to us. This includes:

**Communications:** if you contact us via the website, social media, or email, information is collected.

**Basic account information:** if you register for an account, we collect data such as your name, address, and email address.

**Payment information:** if you sign up for an account, we collect your payment information.

### Information we collect automatically

We also collect some information automatically when you visit the website:

**Cookies:** we use cookies for a variety of reasons, such as to remember who you are logged in as.

Other parties which advertise on our site may use cookies of their own, including [google](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/). When you click on ad links, these services automatically receive information from your browser, such as your ip address, and may use technologies such as cookies, web beacons or javascripts to judge the effectiveness of their ad campaigns or to personalize ad content. This website has no control over the use of cookies or such technology by third party advertisers.

Consulting the respective privacy policies of these advertisers would be the best way to understand how they use your information. If you wish, you can disable cookies through your browser and disallow this kind of information collection. You can learn more about this by consulting the help guide for your internet browser.

**Logs:** we log access to our services in log files, which can include IP address, time and date of access, and the pages visited. We do not report any IP addresses to advertisers.

**Usage information:** we collect information regarding how you’re using the website.

### Information we receive from other sources

We collect information from other sources, which at this time includes Google Analytics, provided by Google Inc. Through the use of cookies, we’re able to analyze how visitors use the website.

### How do we use this information?

We use the information noted in the above section as follows:

**To personal Foreclosuredatabank.com:** we do this to provide a personalized experienced to each visitor.

**To communicate with you regarding Foreclosuredatabank.com:** we use your contact information to sent emails relating to the website. If you have opted-in, you may also receive emails related to promotions, newsletters, etc.

**To resolve customer issues:** when you contact support, we may use your information to find a solution.

**To improve your experience:** we use usage information to identify issues with our site, as to provide a better experience in the future.

**To prevent security issues:** through usage information and logs we can monitor Foreclosuredatabank.com for suspicious activity.

### Nondisclosure

We take great pride in keeping your information safe and secure. For this reason, we never sell, rent or trade your information with third parties without your consent. The only exceptions to this include:

Service providers are working on behalf of Foreclosuredatabank.com, including: CCBill, Inc (United States): Billing and subscriptions.

To comply with laws, such as if we receive a request from a federal, state, or local authority.

### How do we store and secure this information?

Even though no service is 100 percent sure, we do whatever we can to provide a high level of security regarding your information. Your information is stored at the following locations:

**General account and report information:** Foreclosuredatabank.com (United States). We do not store credit card information or any other sensitive information on our own servers.

**Payment information:** CCBill.com (United States). Please review CCBill's Privacy Policy by [clicking here](http://www.ccbill.com/cs/acf/html/privacy_policy-english.html).

### Update and deletion of information

The following data can be accessed and updated:

**General account information:** your name, email, and communication preferences.

**Payment information:** your credit card details can be updated from the Payment Update page at CCBill.

**Test details:** test options (e.g. Cookies, HTTP authentication) can be accessed and updated at any time.

If you want to delete your account or update other forms of data, please contact us with your request.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you can get in touch via the following address (or our [ contact form](https://www.foreclosuredatabank.com/contact-info/)):

Foreclosuredatabank.com  
1800 Sans Souci blvd, 136  
North Miami, FL 33181  
United States

### Changes

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy. We are always looking for ways to improve Foreclosuredatabank.com, but we will never reduce your rights without first asking for consent to the changes. All changes will always be available on Foreclosuredatabank.com.

### When this Privacy Policy applies

This privacy policy is applicable for all services offered on the Foreclosuredatabank.com website. Our website contains links to other online properties. Once you leave our site, the privacy policy is no longer applicable.

### Social media plug-ins and Embedded maps

Foreclosuredatabank.com uses two plug-ins for easy sharing via social media. Here is the information you need:

Facebook, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA

LinkedIn, operated by LinkedIn, 2029 Sterling Court Mountain View, CA 94043 United States.

Being on our website does not automatically result in sharing data on these social media networks. These plugins do not activate until they are clicked. From there, you are taken to the applicable social media platform, which has its own privacy policies.

We also have features that implement with Google Maps’ or Bing Maps’ web mapping data:

Your use of Google Maps is subject to Google’s terms of use. Please [visit here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us) for more information.

Your use of Bing Maps is subject to Microsoft’s privacy policy. Please visit [visit here](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us) for more information.

### Site for Use By U.S. Residents Only

At this time, use of Foreclosuredatabank.com is for United States residents only. The Privacy Policy applies to the processing, storage, collection, use of information submitted by residents of the United States. By using the site, you represent that you are a resident of the United States.

If you are a United States resident using Foreclosuredatabank.com from out of the country, you agree that by accessing the site, your information will be transferred and stored in the United States, as this is where our servers are located.

You also understand that our data protection measures are not necessarily the same as the country from which you are accessing Foreclosuredatabank.com.

### Children's Privacy

All users of Foreclosuredatabank.com must be a minimum of 18 years of age. By using the site, you represent that you at least 18 years of age.

We do not collect information from any person we know to be under the age of 13. Furthermore, no portion of our website is designed or structured to attract users under 13 years of age.

If you know that a child under the age of 13 has shared information with Foreclosuredatabank.com, please contact us immediately.

### Effective Date and Modifications to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 20, 2018.

At Foreclosuredatabank.com, we reserve the right to modify the Privacy Policy at any time. When changes are made, we will notify you by making the updates on the website. We may also notify you of the changes via email.

You are responsible for visiting this page on a regular basis to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent agreement.

Any modification will be effective immediately upon publishing to Foreclosuredatabank.com. Your continued use of the site after posted modifications indicates your acceptance. If you do not accept or agree with the Privacy Policy, you should not use Foreclosuredatabank.com.

### Thank You

We value your patronage and appreciate the time you have taken to read this Privacy and Security Policy. We are serious about personal privacy, and we are committed to staying abreast of the latest technological advancements in the field of digital privacy and protection. We also urge you to read our Terms and Conditions of Use.
